<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Technology &#8211; Publisher</title>
	<atom:link href="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/category/technology/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher</link>
	<description>Publishing platform template for Wordpress</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 10:45:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.4</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Technology &#8211; Publisher</title>
	<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Technology Is Growing Fast and Changing Our Lives Essay</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/technology-is-growing-fast-and-changing-our-lives-essay/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/technology-is-growing-fast-and-changing-our-lives-essay/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 10:37:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=240</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The new technology revolution is creating tremendous value for businesses across the economic spectrum. With so much information technology available that enables millions of companies and professionals to reach new levels of success, it is no wonder how much consumers spend. According to a recent Pew Research Center report, about 25.2% of consumers spend at [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>The new technology revolution</strong> is creating tremendous value for businesses across the economic spectrum.</p>



<p>With so much information technology available that enables millions of companies and professionals to reach new levels of success, it is no wonder how much consumers spend. According to a recent Pew Research Center report, about 25.2% of consumers spend at least some of their purchases online.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><img src="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/undraw_mobile_user_7oqo.min_-1024x618.png" alt="" class="wp-image-610"/></figure>



<blockquote style="text-align:center" class="wp-block-quote is-style-large"><p>Knowledge without action is meaningless.</p><cite>Abu Bakr</cite></blockquote>



<p>Now, with so many choices to choose from, there is always room to expand your business marketing strategy and increase conversions.</p>



<p>If you&#8217;re like most businesses, your sales team has a role in maximizing your business&#8217; ROI and expanding your reach.</p>



<p>The most important step in marketing and promoting your business is developing compelling and creative marketing and promotional materials.</p>



<div class="wp-block-image is-floated"><figure class="alignright"><img src="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/undraw_version_control_9bpv-1024x684.png" alt="" class="wp-image-252"/></figure></div>



<p>Research, write and edit professional business promotional materials in order to create compelling materials that will help your business stand out from the competition. The marketing department will also work with your sales staff to create customized materials where you can add value to your business.</p>



<p>Prove to yourself that the right promotional material will help your company stand out from the competition. Start by studying the top 20 most successful businesses and finding a number of examples that best explain how they did it and explain what the sales team and the marketing department accomplished with them</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/technology-is-growing-fast-and-changing-our-lives-essay/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Becoming a Virtual Reality Designer</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/becoming-a-virtual-reality-designer/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/becoming-a-virtual-reality-designer/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 13:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Virtual Reality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=621</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As VR technology is evolving, it is challenging for designers to use it effectively. Even with years of experience, many traditional design professionals feel stuck, unable to push the limits of immersion, and not able to create virtual prototypes of what they want. In fact, a lot of these conventional industry professionals feel like the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-drop-cap">As VR technology is evolving, it is challenging for designers to use it effectively. Even with years of experience, many traditional design professionals feel stuck, unable to push the limits of immersion, and not able to create virtual prototypes of what they want. In fact, a lot of these conventional industry professionals feel like the technology is &#8220;too big&#8221; and not sufficiently accessible. This leaves us with designers who feel that it is just not possible, because the technology is so abstract or difficult to understand. This disconnect is becoming increasingly apparent in industry.</p>



<div class="wp-block-image is-floated"><figure class="alignright"><img src="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/1629.min_.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-634"/></figure></div>



<p>One common experience of VR developer is the disappointment of being unable to deliver a prototype and learn from it.</p>



<p>The process starts when you start exploring more abstract possibilities with virtual reality. From that start the concept of a &#8220;prototype&#8221; gets abstracted from you and becomes another term for something that is merely a &#8220;proof of concept&#8221;. The concept of an &#8220;actual&#8221; prototype becomes less and less important to you as you move further away from the goal. Your &#8220;pros to learn from&#8221; starts to become meaningless.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p><strong>Becoming a Virtual Reality Designer</strong>&nbsp;is not easy. However the skill that you need to learn can easily be learned even easily.<br></p></blockquote>



<p>I am no different. I worked as a software engineer for many years, and learned many techniques. Now, as a virtual reality designer and web developer, I have grown up with tools which are easily accessible to me, and the knowledge I can gain from developing these types of applications for virtual reality. Therefore I have dedicated myself to learning other virtual reality technologies and tools over the next year or so.</p>



<div class="wp-block-image is-floated"><figure class="alignleft"><img src="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/vr-glasses.min_-1024x527.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-637"/></figure></div>



<p>Here is an example of what I am currently learning. I recently attended the 3rd VR World Congress (VRWorlds) from January 11th to 28th, 2016. I had a chance to speak with a number of interesting developers who were passionate about VR and VR-related topics. </p>



<p>We had a fascinating time, and one of the things I learned is that while virtual reality is growing, there still needs to be dedicated resources for it. While most of our community are currently focused on building VR demos and training for VR players, there is still a large amount of work to be done.</p>



<p>So I have focused my efforts on creating dedicated resources for virtual reality in general and for VR games specifically for all platforms.</p>



<p>There are various forums and community groups, forums, and forum support programs online, but there still needs to be dedicated dedicated resources dedicated to virtual reality for PC</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/becoming-a-virtual-reality-designer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to easily do Object Detection on Drone Imagery using Deep learning</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/how-to-easily-do-object-detection-on-drone-imagery-using-deep-learning/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/how-to-easily-do-object-detection-on-drone-imagery-using-deep-learning/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 09:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Drone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tutorials]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=516</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There are also ways to easily detect objects in complex programs without even doing the object detection yourself. For example, to detect arrays, you have to know exactly what values they contain (this will be explained in more detail later). How to easily do Object Detection with Javacsript Consider the following JavaScript code. The variable [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-drop-cap">There are also ways to easily detect objects in complex programs without even doing the object detection yourself. For example, to detect arrays, you have to know exactly what values they contain (this will be explained in more detail later).</p>



<h4><strong>How to easily do Object Detection with Javacsript</strong></h4>



<p>Consider the following JavaScript code. The variable name contains 2 items (i.e. a comma-separated array). A user can check the number of items inside of the array by writing &#8220;foo&#8221; as &#8220;1,2,3&#8221;;</p>



<pre class="wp-block-preformatted wp-block-svq-code prettyprint">var array = [1] + "Baz";
var foo = [1,2];
for (var i = 1; i &lt;= array.length; i++) {
foo[i] = 5;
}</pre>



<div class="wp-block-image is-floated"><figure class="alignleft"><img src="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/548.min_.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-541"/></figure></div>



<p>A few years ago I worked on a new project called Signal Detection and Recognition, which uses an X-Ray image acquired during spaceflight to identify spacecraft.</p>



<p>I wrote that implementation in C and then ran the program against it using gdb.</p>



<p>In this post we will explain how that was done. You can read my prior post about the implementation here; if you enjoy this blog, we can also discuss the new feature in Go here or the upcoming rewrite of X-Ray to work better with Go.</p>



<p>Now let&#8217;s dive into the very easy part of Object <sup class="svq-sidelink" data-svq-note="3"><a href="javascript:void(0)" >3</a></sup><span class="svq-sidenote will-animate" data-cssanimate="fadeIn" data-svq-note="3">Object-oriented programming(OOP) is aprogramming paradigm based on the concept of &#8220;objects&#8221;, which can contain data, in the form of fields, and code, in the form ofprocedures (often known as methotds).</span> detection with us. We will learn how one uses the Javacript language to understand some common constructs.</p>



<p>This includes understanding the syntax of some common patterns and patterns like the return types of Javacript and how to generate a class of some class. Before we step away from Javacript though, here is your first piece of Java Object detection with us.</p>



<h6>OCR Function:</h6>



<pre class="wp-block-preformatted wp-block-svq-code prettyprint">recognitionImageElement.addEventListener('change', () =&gt; {
 if (!recognitionImageElement.files) {
   return null;
 }
const file = recognitionImageElement.files[0];
})</pre>



<h6>Dealing with the&nbsp;result:</h6>



<p>The result of the <code>.recognition()</code> method <sup class="svq-sidelink" data-svq-note="4"><a href="javascript:void(0)" >4</a></sup><span class="svq-sidenote will-animate" data-cssanimate="fadeIn" data-svq-note="4">A method in object-oriented programming (OOP) is a procedure asociated with a message and an object. An object consists of data and behavior. The data and behavior comprise an interface, which specifies how the object may be utilized by any of various consumers of the object.</span> is confusing, to say the least. It is not well documented and so we have to deduce some things on our own:</p>



<pre class="wp-block-preformatted wp-block-svq-code prettyprint">{
    blocks: Array[1]
    confidence: 87
    html: "&lt;div class='ocr_page' id='page_1' ..."
    lines: Array[3]
    oem: "DEFAULT"
    paragraphs: Array[1]
    psm: "SINGLE_BLOCK"
    symbols: Array[33]
    text: "Hello World↵from beyond↵the Cosmic Void↵↵"
    version: "3.04.00"
    words: Array[7]
}</pre>



<h6>Conclusion</h6>



<p>The Javascript library provides us with a ready-to-use OCR implementation that is efficient and, for the most part, accurate. The additional advantage of the library is its immense flexibility thanks to being compatible with both Node.js and a browser. There is even an option to include custom training data which could make it work better for your specific applications.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/how-to-easily-do-object-detection-on-drone-imagery-using-deep-learning/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>5</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Don’t Make Me Think: 20 Wise Thoughts about Usability</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/dont-make-me-think-20-wise-thoughts-about-usability/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/dont-make-me-think-20-wise-thoughts-about-usability/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 08:04:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Usability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=274</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[You&#8217;ll learn and apply these tools, and help us get better. You&#8217;ll learn about the basics of writing, editing, visual and audio skills, which will help you to: Create more content. Write more professionally. Make better decisions about your work and what your goals should be. In addition, we&#8217;ll explain how to make your work [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>You&#8217;ll learn and apply these tools, and help us get better. You&#8217;ll learn about the basics of writing, editing, visual and audio skills, which will help you to:</p>



<ul><li>Create more content.</li><li>Write more professionally.</li><li>Make better decisions about your work and what your goals should be.</li><li>In addition, we&#8217;ll explain how to make your work more enjoyable.</li><li>And help you become a stronger writer by improving your writing and problem-solving skills.</li></ul>



<h6>You&#8217;ll also learn to:</h6>



<ul><li>Take your project skills very seriously.</li><li>Avoid distractions so you can concentrate on writing the work you want to get done.</li><li>Learn how to create and write original content and share to encourage your friends to help you discover and write in the future.</li><li>How to get started with content development, especially using HTML and CSS.</li><li>Design tips to make your writing more engaging.</li></ul>



<p>If you&#8217;re interested to learn more about the technology behind this ebook, I would ask you to sign up for our newsletter at the top of this page. You&#8217;ll automatically have an invite if you do that. I&#8217;d recommend reading this too to see the basic tools and techniques of writing, formatting, and printing. You will find the source code behind Python below.</p>



<p>If you want some inspiration of different ways of expressing your thoughts through visual media, check out this blog post.</p>



<hr class="wp-block-separator is-style-dots" />



<p>There are going to be times when you don&#8217;t know what to do for the most part right away, whether it&#8217;s your children or whether it&#8217;s your spouse at home. This gives you a really good time, because when you realize, &#8216;I need to look at something, how can I get that done?&#8217;</p>



<p>What&#8217;s so great about &#8220;thinking about your feelings first&#8221;—especially when you find it&#8217;s in a place people can relate to? So can you! This is where &#8220;déjà vu&#8221; comes in!</p>



<h4>The Power of Emotion</h4>



<p>For me, the best advice I can give you about thinking in terms of feelings is that emotions are what really makes your life feel interesting.</p>



<p>Movies are filled with strong emotions, and even at the end there are scenes of tears and grief and just general sadness.</p>



<p>That&#8217;s what we see the movie with. We need to recognize the power of emotions so that we don&#8217;t run from the emotions. When you know you&#8217;re going to cry, understand the significance of making an emotional connection with a character that isn&#8217;t quite there yet, even though it hurts. And when you don&#8217;t know exactly what someone&#8217;s feeling, you&#8217;re better equipped to empathize, so don&#8217;t worry about it if it doesn&#8217;t feel right, for example.</p>



<hr class="wp-block-separator is-style-dots" />



<p>Movies tell a story of people in emotional states of grief. The film has an enormous amount of scenes of people losing friends, friends of friends, losing each other — you get to see that kind of thing — and that&#8217;s not the most comfortable thing to watch.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-style-large"><p>Making every page or screen self-evident is like having good lighting in a store: it just makes everything seem better.</p><cite>Steve Krug</cite></blockquote>



<p>There are scenes where he&#8217;s losing him mother as well, and that&#8217;s not necessarily the most emotionally wrenching thing to watch. When you know what you&#8217;re getting into because a script is written, even a lot of things like that are pretty good. Also, we often have to look at how we&#8217;re approaching certain things, for example when it comes to the idea of forgiveness or forgiveness itself. These are big things, because they&#8217;re very personal things.&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/dont-make-me-think-20-wise-thoughts-about-usability/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Rise of Type Design</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/flat-design-and-the-rise-of-type-design/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/flat-design-and-the-rise-of-type-design/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 09:43:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Flat design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Graphics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=371</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[When the designers of Flat Design created their first prototype of the typeface, they had one simple goal, which was to create a universal, attractive and memorable typeface. They wanted to create both a style and a typefaces – something which had no specific name, like &#8216;L&#8217; in the French capital. These are all well [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-drop-cap">When the designers of Flat Design created their first prototype of the typeface, they had one simple goal, which was to create a universal, attractive and memorable typeface. They wanted to create both a style and a typefaces – something which had no specific name, like &#8216;L&#8217; in the French capital. These are all well established rules that designers follow when they have a project in mind like this, but for Flat, it was a lot more complex and they had no idea how to do it. The typefaces to be the basis of their flat design philosophy was very much on their own minds, especially the two that they chose.</p>



<p>With all it&#8217;s features, Flat Design was the creation of four people; Martin, Martin Martinovich, Martin Reindl, and Paul Reindl. Martin gave his sidenote Rails display optional accompanying content outside of the main viewport of your website. <sq-note>Sites often use sidenotes content to fix additional often optional content to your viewport as you scroll through the page.</sq-note> content and helped with the design by using his personal experience as an artist in Paris.</p>



<p>He also gave away a lot of feedback during the design process, which helped shape the new project of Flat Design. The most important thing Martin asked for was consistency; as he always tried to use typefaces with subtle contrasts to distinguish them from each other. With his experience, Martin wanted to make a new design in response to his own needs, which led to the addition of three unique designs.</p>



<div class="wp-block-image is-floated"><figure class="alignleft"><img src="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/56515.min_.png" alt="" class="wp-image-862" srcset="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/56515.min_.png 800w, https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/56515.min_-300x268.png 300w, https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/56515.min_-768x686.png 768w, https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/56515.min_-45x40.png 45w" sizes="(min-width: 960px) 75vw, 100vw" /></figure></div>



<p>In a recent interview with Wired, the inventor of the flat design, Peter Thiel, talked more about his theory of why the flat shape works and what you can do to create a flat design.</p>



<p>I think a flat design is very, very important because it helps us to understand that the shape and the way we think about shapes, shapes and their functions are so strongly interconnected. We&#8217;re very, very influenced by each other, but also deeply connected. What we&#8217;re going against is that we try to do a lot of things with a flat design that&#8217;s going to create a lot of pain and we&#8217;re doing that by having very different approaches to what shape should be.</p>



<p>And what we have in the past is very simplistic.</p>



<p>There&#8217;s a really big assumption that we make that we&#8217;re going to get rid of all the things but the form of the design is more important than these things. You get rid of these forms and you get rid of this form of form, and that can make this thing seem rigid because you&#8217;re putting more emphasis on that shape and this other form that&#8217;s completely abstract and abstract.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/flat-design-and-the-rise-of-type-design/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>4</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Become a Better Version of Yourself</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/how-to-become-a-better-version-of-yourself-today/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/how-to-become-a-better-version-of-yourself-today/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 08:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Productivity]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=296</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[You probably think it&#8217;s important to work out more and eat better but I find that most of the time I just do what I have in the bank. If I eat healthier, I don&#8217;t have as much money. In all reality you don&#8217;t need to work out every day to get your money where [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>You probably think it&#8217;s important to work out more and eat better but I find that most of the time I just do what I have in the bank. If I eat healthier, I don&#8217;t have as much money. In all reality you don&#8217;t need to work out every day to get your money where it needs to be. </p>



<p>I&#8217;ve made some pretty bad habits in my life that I don&#8217;t want to repeat.</p>



<p>If you have been through some difficult times and need help getting over them it&#8217;s not because you can&#8217;t get the money. It&#8217;s not because spending more money is easier than saving it. It&#8217;s because you need a positive attitude. It&#8217;s because you need to realize a need.</p>



<p>I can work with me, I can make excuses, and yes I am willing to pay for it. I love getting work done and helping people get better too. But that&#8217;s the only way I can get it done. So, let&#8217;s talk about why.</p>



<h5>Why do I love getting work done?</h5>



<p>I get things done in a time that is much more rewarding to me than work and that is when I enjoy how work is done. Sometimes this is done by doing simple things with my hands rather than trying to accomplish every single little task with your body or your mind.</p>



<p>People who don&#8217;t live a typical American life are taught by TV and pop-culture to believe that everything will end for them one day. Many of these are not the most successful people out there, because they simply take their chances that life will be tough. They don&#8217;t have the money to buy their way out of debt. They&#8217;re constantly worried that they&#8217;ll lose their jobs, their homes, and their lives.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><a href="#_"><img src="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/banner_add.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-2278" srcset="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/banner_add.jpg 728w, https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/banner_add-300x37.jpg 300w, https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/banner_add-45x6.jpg 45w" sizes="(min-width: 960px) 75vw, 100vw" /></a></figure>



<p>Others of these parents do the exact opposite. In my experience, these people aren&#8217;t necessarily the worst people out there – at least not at the bottom.</p>



<p>They&#8217;re also not as financially stable as the typical American parent and are, at least from what I see, quite aware of what they are likely headed for.</p>



<p>So, I think it&#8217;s only fair for us to ask ourselves what motivates each person that you talk to, or that you talk to in person.</p>



<p>For today&#8217;s post, I&#8217;m going to take that question of what motivates this author and try to come up with a set of actions to take as you consider that you&#8217;re going to be the subject of someone else</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/how-to-become-a-better-version-of-yourself-today/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
