<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Motivation &#8211; Publisher</title>
	<atom:link href="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/tag/motivation/feed/?layout=boxed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher</link>
	<description>Publishing platform template for Wordpress</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 11:28:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.4</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Motivation &#8211; Publisher</title>
	<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>What is an Influencer?</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/what-is-an-influencer/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/what-is-an-influencer/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mangusta Rust]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 08:37:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Worldwide]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Productivity]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/?p=982</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[An influencer is someone who has a large following within the product or service, and can influence customers or potential customers to take a particular action. I&#8217;ve written before about how the &#8220;social media manager&#8221; is key to building a successful product, and why influencers are key to building strong brand authority as well. How [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-drop-cap">An influencer is someone who has a large following within the product or service, and can influence customers or potential customers to take a particular action.</p>



<p>I&#8217;ve written before about how the &#8220;social media manager&#8221; is key to building a successful product, and why influencers are key to building strong brand authority as well.</p>



<p>How do you build influencers? Here is the process:</p>



<p>Create a goal – Set a target audience and set the goal. Use social media platforms to gather this &#8220;know your consumer&#8221; information. Determine the right people to target. Look to identify influencers you know that have a strong following on each channel, and use them to help you reach those customers. Invite the influencers you&#8217;ve identified to be part of your product, or product launch.</p>



<p>This process will help you create strong relationships with influencers using social media. By following my advice, you can build strong influence within a short amount of time.</p>



<h4>How to Find An Influencer?</h4>



<p>One of the best ways to find an influencers online is to find them on social media and on social networks like Facebook and Twitter.</p>



<p>For example, here are some of their sites/websites that would make an excellent candidate as part of your online outreach:</p>



<h6><strong>Instagram</strong></h6>



<p>Instagram offers several good ways to get involved with Instagram or any other social network.</p>



<p>Follow the Instagram Community on social media sites like Twitter and Facebook.</p>



<p>Follow the Instagram community on Instagram to find influencers who have a particular niche in Instagram and the influencers will usually post their photos to their social media accounts, as well.</p>



<p>Follow the Instagram Community to help them promote your Instagram products / services.</p>



<p>If you want to learn how to become featured in Instagram then head to this Instagram website and sign-up for the Instagram Insider Program.</p>



<h6><strong>Facebook</strong></h6>



<p>Facebook is the main social networking site by a country mile. Therefore, it has an incredible amount of potential.<br></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/what-is-an-influencer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>3</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The best time to plant a tree was 20 years ago. The second best time is now.</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/the-best-time-to-plant-a-tree-was-20-years-ago-the-second-best-time-is-now/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/the-best-time-to-plant-a-tree-was-20-years-ago-the-second-best-time-is-now/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mangusta Rust]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 09:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Good Reads]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Quotes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chinese Proverb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Productivity]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=306</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The best time to plant a tree was 20 years ago. The second best time is now. Chinese Proverb … what this Chinese Proverb means to you now? Basically in&#160;the context of the conversation here today, this means that if you want success and growth in the future, the best time to act is now.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-style-large"><p>The best time to plant a tree was 20 years ago. The second best time is now.</p><cite>Chinese Proverb</cite></blockquote>



<h6>… what this Chinese Proverb means to you now?</h6>



<p>Basically in&nbsp;the context of the conversation here today, this means that if you want success and growth in the future, the best time to act is now.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/the-best-time-to-plant-a-tree-was-20-years-ago-the-second-best-time-is-now/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>5 Things to Do When You Have Too Many Ideas and Never Finish Anything.</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/5-things-to-do-when-you-have-too-many-ideas-and-never-finish-anything/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/5-things-to-do-when-you-have-too-many-ideas-and-never-finish-anything/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 08:50:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Good Reads]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Productivity]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=292</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Things to Do When You Have Too Many Ideas and Never Finish Anything.&#160;I&#8217;d love to see your ideas here. What is your favorite thing when you have too many ideas? What I&#8217;ve learned about life: When you have an idea on your hands, it&#8217;s time to tackle a few of those things and see if [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Things to Do When You Have Too Many Ideas and Never Finish Anything.</strong>&nbsp;I&#8217;d love to see your ideas here. What is your favorite thing when you have too many ideas?</p>



<p>What I&#8217;ve learned about life: When you have an idea on your hands, it&#8217;s time to tackle a few of those things and see if you can put everything together before you write anything down.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>I have too many ideas for a lifetime.</p><cite>Taylor Wilson</cite></blockquote>



<p>What I&#8217;ve learned about my life: You really don&#8217;t have to chase ideas as you have no problem following them to your end goal.</p>



<p>What I&#8217;ve learned about myself and others: A lot of advice works and I recommend that you find that great group of people that you can go to on Facebook/E-mail and chat with everyday when you feel like the conversation isn&#8217;t really going anywhere.</p>



<p>What I&#8217;ve learned about myself and my business; I use it as fuel when I have too much ideas to think of anything or it isn&#8217;t going well with business.</p>



<p>How to Get Your Ideas to Work; If you&#8217;re too lazy to find them out, it&#8217;s possible to start this habit today.</p>



<p>Decide If Your Book Idea is Too New and Can&#8217;t Wait to Learn Everything About It. &#8220;If I decide to pursue an idea that&#8217;s already out there, it will make me far more creative. As far as waiting for a book to be developed, I always plan my time so I&#8217;ll be reading one book every three months.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/5-things-to-do-when-you-have-too-many-ideas-and-never-finish-anything/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How the World’s Most Successful Founders Approach Failure</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/how-the-worlds-most-successful-founders-approach-failure/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/how-the-worlds-most-successful-founders-approach-failure/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 08:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Good Reads]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Productivity]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=280</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[From what we&#8217;ve learned from their successes, we&#8217;ve designed a set of lessons to lead successful founders to their next success. The core ideas are: Treat your life like a game or a martial art,” says Dalio. “Your mission is to figure out how to get around your challenges to get to your goals. In [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-drop-cap">From what we&#8217;ve learned from their successes, we&#8217;ve designed a set of lessons to lead successful founders to their next success. The core ideas are:</p>



<p><strong>Treat your life like a game or a martial art,” says Dalio. “Your mission is to figure out how to get around your challenges to get to your goals. In the process of playing the game or practicing this martial art, you will become more skilled. As you get better, you will progress to ever-higher levels of the game that will require — and teach you — greater skills.</strong></p>



<p>Be fearless. When someone takes you seriously, you learn to believe they have the same drive you do. If they fail because you&#8217;re not listening, they&#8217;re failing because you&#8217;re too scared to try.</p>



<div class="wp-block-image is-floated"><figure class="alignleft"><img src="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/579260-plvyra-985.min_-1024x684.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-665"/></figure></div>



<p>When someone takes you seriously, you learn to believe they have the same drive you do. If they fail because you&#8217;re not listening, they&#8217;re failing because you&#8217;re too scared to try.</p>



<p>Look for new ways to fail. We&#8217;re all pretty good at trying something new, whether that&#8217;s making the first pitch at your job or a startup, but it isn&#8217;t always going to work out the way you want. Instead, be brave enough to fail.</p>



<p>Remember that failure is a chance to take steps in the right direction and learn from your mistakes, not a guarantee.</p>



<p>Successful Founders Program <sup class="svq-sidelink" data-svq-note="2"><a href="javascript:void(0)" >2</a></sup><span class="svq-sidenote will-animate" data-cssanimate="fadeIn" data-svq-note="2">Founders Program is a program offering founding for students to apply to the prestigious Standard Graduate School of Business.</span>  Participants may also earn an additional 10% if they have a current or former employer that has provided them with financial support to support their company. To get started, submit your details for an Interview Request form.</p>



<p>This event offers a one-time 10% bonus that&#8217;s paid in cash. If you complete your own startup and receive funding through your own fundraising team, then you get it back.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><a href="#_"><img src="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/banner_add.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-2278" srcset="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/banner_add.jpg 728w, https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/banner_add-300x37.jpg 300w, https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/banner_add-45x6.jpg 45w" sizes="(min-width: 960px) 75vw, 100vw" /></a></figure>



<p>You don&#8217;t need to know that you&#8217;re smart enough or powerful enough to succeed, nor does it mean you don&#8217;t need to invest a lot of time or money in learning from your mistakes.&nbsp;</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>Life is a succession of lessons which must be lived to be understood.</p><cite>Helen Keller</cite></blockquote>



<p>The key is learning how to succeed from failure. You can&#8217;t just rely on failures for validation &#8211; you have to find ways to be more confident in your abilities.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/how-the-worlds-most-successful-founders-approach-failure/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Goodreads Quote</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/goodreads-quote/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/goodreads-quote/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 13:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Good Reads]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Quotes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=94</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[When one door of happiness closes, another opens; but often we look so long at the closed door that we do not see the one which has been opened for us. Helen Keller Explain what is quotes? This is a great opportunity to have an actual conversation about this. Let&#8217;s say you can think of [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>When one door of happiness closes, another opens; but often we look so long at the closed door that we do not see the one which has been opened for us.</p><cite><strong>Helen Keller</strong></cite></blockquote>



<p><strong>Explain what is quotes</strong>? This is a great opportunity to have an actual conversation about this.</p>



<p>Let&#8217;s say you can think of the above quote and you can also think of any other questions you have which could make the quote more interesting and relevant in terms of what we learned. You could start a conversation with your teacher then write what you are curious about down on paper to read the quote. It is important to use your teacher&#8217;s knowledge of the subject matter to help you think up your own question or thought.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/goodreads-quote/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>4</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
