<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Usability &#8211; Publisher</title>
	<atom:link href="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/tag/usability/feed/?layout=boxed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher</link>
	<description>Publishing platform template for Wordpress</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 08:04:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.4</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Usability &#8211; Publisher</title>
	<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Don’t Make Me Think: 20 Wise Thoughts about Usability</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/dont-make-me-think-20-wise-thoughts-about-usability/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/dont-make-me-think-20-wise-thoughts-about-usability/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 08:04:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Usability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=274</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[You&#8217;ll learn and apply these tools, and help us get better. You&#8217;ll learn about the basics of writing, editing, visual and audio skills, which will help you to: Create more content. Write more professionally. Make better decisions about your work and what your goals should be. In addition, we&#8217;ll explain how to make your work [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>You&#8217;ll learn and apply these tools, and help us get better. You&#8217;ll learn about the basics of writing, editing, visual and audio skills, which will help you to:</p>



<ul><li>Create more content.</li><li>Write more professionally.</li><li>Make better decisions about your work and what your goals should be.</li><li>In addition, we&#8217;ll explain how to make your work more enjoyable.</li><li>And help you become a stronger writer by improving your writing and problem-solving skills.</li></ul>



<h6>You&#8217;ll also learn to:</h6>



<ul><li>Take your project skills very seriously.</li><li>Avoid distractions so you can concentrate on writing the work you want to get done.</li><li>Learn how to create and write original content and share to encourage your friends to help you discover and write in the future.</li><li>How to get started with content development, especially using HTML and CSS.</li><li>Design tips to make your writing more engaging.</li></ul>



<p>If you&#8217;re interested to learn more about the technology behind this ebook, I would ask you to sign up for our newsletter at the top of this page. You&#8217;ll automatically have an invite if you do that. I&#8217;d recommend reading this too to see the basic tools and techniques of writing, formatting, and printing. You will find the source code behind Python below.</p>



<p>If you want some inspiration of different ways of expressing your thoughts through visual media, check out this blog post.</p>



<hr class="wp-block-separator is-style-dots" />



<p>There are going to be times when you don&#8217;t know what to do for the most part right away, whether it&#8217;s your children or whether it&#8217;s your spouse at home. This gives you a really good time, because when you realize, &#8216;I need to look at something, how can I get that done?&#8217;</p>



<p>What&#8217;s so great about &#8220;thinking about your feelings first&#8221;—especially when you find it&#8217;s in a place people can relate to? So can you! This is where &#8220;déjà vu&#8221; comes in!</p>



<h4>The Power of Emotion</h4>



<p>For me, the best advice I can give you about thinking in terms of feelings is that emotions are what really makes your life feel interesting.</p>



<p>Movies are filled with strong emotions, and even at the end there are scenes of tears and grief and just general sadness.</p>



<p>That&#8217;s what we see the movie with. We need to recognize the power of emotions so that we don&#8217;t run from the emotions. When you know you&#8217;re going to cry, understand the significance of making an emotional connection with a character that isn&#8217;t quite there yet, even though it hurts. And when you don&#8217;t know exactly what someone&#8217;s feeling, you&#8217;re better equipped to empathize, so don&#8217;t worry about it if it doesn&#8217;t feel right, for example.</p>



<hr class="wp-block-separator is-style-dots" />



<p>Movies tell a story of people in emotional states of grief. The film has an enormous amount of scenes of people losing friends, friends of friends, losing each other — you get to see that kind of thing — and that&#8217;s not the most comfortable thing to watch.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-style-large"><p>Making every page or screen self-evident is like having good lighting in a store: it just makes everything seem better.</p><cite>Steve Krug</cite></blockquote>



<p>There are scenes where he&#8217;s losing him mother as well, and that&#8217;s not necessarily the most emotionally wrenching thing to watch. When you know what you&#8217;re getting into because a script is written, even a lot of things like that are pretty good. Also, we often have to look at how we&#8217;re approaching certain things, for example when it comes to the idea of forgiveness or forgiveness itself. These are big things, because they&#8217;re very personal things.&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/dont-make-me-think-20-wise-thoughts-about-usability/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
