<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Worldwide &#8211; Publisher</title>
	<atom:link href="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/category/worldwide/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher</link>
	<description>Publishing platform template for Wordpress</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 15:16:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.4</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Worldwide &#8211; Publisher</title>
	<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Balance of Nature</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/the-balance-of-nature/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/the-balance-of-nature/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mangusta Rust]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 08:24:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Worldwide]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=176</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This is the way a new universe is supposed to work, or at least, how the universe has to work, if it is supposed to. If all the things in the universe (like every single cell, tree, galaxy, star, planet, etc.) can only be understood if you accept that they were created in some very [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-drop-cap">This is the way a new universe is supposed to work, or at least, how the universe has to work, if it is supposed to.</p>



<p>If all the things in the universe (like every single cell, tree, galaxy, star, planet, etc.) can only be understood if you accept that they were created in some very particular manner, then there is no logical possibility to think that they created at all. If you think about it, we&#8217;ve found out a whole lot about the universe (and every single part of it), and we can&#8217;t accept anything as fact unless there is a logical reason for it.</p>



<div class="wp-block-image is-floated"><figure class="alignright"><img src="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/undraw_mobile_user_7oqo.min_-1024x618.png" alt="" class="wp-image-610"/></figure></div>



<p>You can&#8217;t say &#8216;it&#8217; created out of nothing until you&#8217;ve measured something, or figured out the speed of light and the mass of the sun and the mass of matter that they&#8217;re all made of, etc &#8211; at that point all we say is &#8216;something&#8217; creates stuff (and it only works for one case; it can&#8217;t be true for every case, since it&#8217;s impossible to know what might or might not have happened). So then we either have to accept that everything in nature is random, or if that&#8217;s the case, we just don&#8217;t expect the universe to continue to be random.</p>



<p>There&#8217;s a real question here, and the best answer is that you should be willing to consider, but don&#8217;t think that</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>When we talk about animals then they can be considered species, but this is a false and illogical concept. Species do not exist. Humans are one, all animals are one, they are one.</p><p></p></blockquote>



<p>No wonder people say &#8216;the woods are the home of the wild&#8217;. &nbsp;So I&#8217;ve never been there before, it&#8217;s been hard to get here from Seattle. My first few days were amazing, I had a lot of freedom. &nbsp;I was free to make wild food, to use fire, go where I wanted (like hiking, kayaking, or snowshoeing), to climb any mountain, to just go wherever I thought might be interesting. This was around August. </p>



<div class="wp-block-image is-floated"><figure class="alignright"><img src="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/undraw_a_moment_to_relax_bbpa.min_-1024x774.png" alt="" class="wp-image-611"/></figure></div>



<p>So my expectations were way off, my first day of freedom was August 25th. &nbsp;I didn&#8217;t really expect to see any bears there. &nbsp;I think I was going to kill a little one on my snowshoes, but it just sort of disappeared.</p>



<p>I guess I&#8217;m just the weirdo that likes the outdoors. &nbsp;I had my dogs with me, they were amazing with their food. &nbsp;I was taking them for walks, they would run and chase every bit of wildlife they came across, it wasn&#8217;t long at all before someone would come running towards them telling them there was a bear. &nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/the-balance-of-nature/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>7</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What is an Influencer?</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/what-is-an-influencer/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/what-is-an-influencer/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mangusta Rust]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 08:37:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Worldwide]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Productivity]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/?p=982</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[An influencer is someone who has a large following within the product or service, and can influence customers or potential customers to take a particular action. I&#8217;ve written before about how the &#8220;social media manager&#8221; is key to building a successful product, and why influencers are key to building strong brand authority as well. How [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-drop-cap">An influencer is someone who has a large following within the product or service, and can influence customers or potential customers to take a particular action.</p>



<p>I&#8217;ve written before about how the &#8220;social media manager&#8221; is key to building a successful product, and why influencers are key to building strong brand authority as well.</p>



<p>How do you build influencers? Here is the process:</p>



<p>Create a goal – Set a target audience and set the goal. Use social media platforms to gather this &#8220;know your consumer&#8221; information. Determine the right people to target. Look to identify influencers you know that have a strong following on each channel, and use them to help you reach those customers. Invite the influencers you&#8217;ve identified to be part of your product, or product launch.</p>



<p>This process will help you create strong relationships with influencers using social media. By following my advice, you can build strong influence within a short amount of time.</p>



<h4>How to Find An Influencer?</h4>



<p>One of the best ways to find an influencers online is to find them on social media and on social networks like Facebook and Twitter.</p>



<p>For example, here are some of their sites/websites that would make an excellent candidate as part of your online outreach:</p>



<h6><strong>Instagram</strong></h6>



<p>Instagram offers several good ways to get involved with Instagram or any other social network.</p>



<p>Follow the Instagram Community on social media sites like Twitter and Facebook.</p>



<p>Follow the Instagram community on Instagram to find influencers who have a particular niche in Instagram and the influencers will usually post their photos to their social media accounts, as well.</p>



<p>Follow the Instagram Community to help them promote your Instagram products / services.</p>



<p>If you want to learn how to become featured in Instagram then head to this Instagram website and sign-up for the Instagram Insider Program.</p>



<h6><strong>Facebook</strong></h6>



<p>Facebook is the main social networking site by a country mile. Therefore, it has an incredible amount of potential.<br></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/what-is-an-influencer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>3</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fitness Truths Nobody Will Tell You</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/fitness-truths-nobody-will-tell-you/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/fitness-truths-nobody-will-tell-you/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 16:03:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Gallery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Worldwide]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Worlwide]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=701</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[We were raised like children, and our mothers told us how to behave, but most of our time growing up was spent worrying about getting through the day without a scratch. We were taught to believe that we could be a grown man and make it at the gym. We were taught to believe, but [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-drop-cap">We were raised like children, and our mothers told us how to behave, but most of our time growing up was spent worrying about getting through the day without a scratch. We were taught to believe that we could be a grown man and make it at the gym.</p>



<p>We were taught to believe, but we also had to be disciplined and taught how to behave in the gym so we would stay in shape.</p>



<p>Some of us could not get in the gym, so it was only men we found who were fit, but we needed the rest of the girls for help.</p>



<p>My mum is in pain. No wonder she cannot get in the gym because her muscles are weak. I am in pain. My mother&#8217;s strength needs to rest.</p>



<p>We are young kids trying to understand who we are after all. In many countries, these very young girls are killed, beaten, and abandoned as they come into contact with these vicious and illegal sports. We are the victims of violence in our sport. It is the end of innocence for so many and yet, our sport is still alive because of violence.</p>



<p>We are too young to realise that, at the cost of our lives and health, we are doing this to ourselves and others.<br></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/fitness-truths-nobody-will-tell-you/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Flying with Drone Above the City</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/flying-with-drone-above-the-city/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/flying-with-drone-above-the-city/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 10:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Worldwide]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Worlwide]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=540</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To reach the city, get to the intersection the city goes to. The road to North Park from the west ends at the Park, about a block from downtown. From downtown, you must turn left and travel 1/2 mile to the intersection of North Park and South Park with a parking area about 1 mile [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-drop-cap">To reach the city, get to the intersection the city goes to. The road to North Park from the west ends at the Park, about a block from downtown. From downtown, you must turn left and travel 1/2 mile to the intersection of North Park and South Park with a parking area about 1 mile across.</p>



<p>The intersection is at the north side of the city, across from the Civic Center, the Blue Line (a bit higher), the Metra-Civic Center bus loop, the North Park Community Center, and many other places in the city.</p>



<p>Cities reflect the social and economic structures that the people in our towns and cities developed for themselves as their people and as their community.</p>



<div class="wp-block-image is-floated"><figure class="alignright"><img src="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/2183.min_-1024x683.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-556"/></figure></div>



<p>They are also the tools through which people negotiate and co-exist with one another over time through mutual recognition of common interests or grievances, shared property rights and benefits or joint labor activities.</p>



<p>The relationships of citizens to those of their neighbors and of those of their nation&#8217;s government to those of others reflects what&#8217;s common in people&#8217;s lives, whether that be familial relations, shared interests or common customs, language.</p>



<p>If these aspects of our history don&#8217;t appeal to you, I would love to hear from you. Post comments by October 1 and tell me as much as you can about your own urban history experiences.</p>



<p>A map of all available worlds to visit. A tool which allows you to choose any world you wish to visit.<br></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/flying-with-drone-above-the-city/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Neon Metropolis: Your city in fantasy</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/modern-metropolis-your-city-in-fantasy/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/modern-metropolis-your-city-in-fantasy/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Gabriel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 15:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Worldwide]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Worlwide]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=457</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Metropolis is indeed an ancient city, but this would not explain why it looks like a city of a million square feet, and not another of the great ancient cities of Greek or Roman antiquity. There are many theories for what caused this. For instance, there was an event known as the fall of [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-drop-cap">The Metropolis is indeed an ancient city, but this would not explain why it looks like a city of a million square feet, and not another of the great ancient cities of Greek or Roman antiquity. There are many theories for what caused this. For instance, there was an event known as the fall of Atlantis that happened somewhere between the second century BCE and the fourth century CE.</p>



<p>What do we find in all this ancient knowledge? Most Greek and Roman monuments are much less complex and, in many cases, almost impossible to identify. The Metropolis is a monument that dates to the middle ages. It is a great stone monument of the Iron Age, an ancient city built in the form of a walled district. The ancient Greek writers were far more detailed with the monuments they created and did not only discuss the nature of the walls, but they spoke about a great many other buildings of this great civilization. I will mention just one of the other famous monuments, the great pyramid or pyramids built by the Sumerians. This great pyramid, known as the Great Pyramid, is in Iraq, and was located on the south side of the mountain known as Mount Sinir.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/modern-metropolis-your-city-in-fantasy/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>One Thing That Never Changes About Online Marketing</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/one-thing-that-never-changes-about-online-marketing/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/one-thing-that-never-changes-about-online-marketing/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 14:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Worldwide]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Goodreads]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=432</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[So what exactly was so hard about &#8220;Not Your Business&#8221;? The bottom line: If you&#8217;re a small business looking to grow online, it&#8217;s tough. It takes a lot of resources, effort and money. In fact, your success will be measured by whether you can get your content delivered on time — as opposed to just [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>So what exactly was so hard about &#8220;Not Your Business&#8221;? The bottom line: If you&#8217;re a small business looking to grow online, it&#8217;s tough. It takes a lot of resources, effort and money. In fact, your success will be measured by whether you can get your content delivered on time — as opposed to just getting it through your &#8220;recreational&#8221; business — even once you&#8217;ve created your business (remember all the times you say you don&#8217;t want to make money?).</p>



<p>You may be thinking that&#8217;s because you&#8217;re not making money, so the idea is ridiculous. That said, one thing that never changes is that it&#8217;s hard to stay out of your own little bubble.</p>



<p>At one point a friend of mine who was a graphic designer just started a blog named &#8220;How To Make A Living Online.&#8221; He was a big time content creator, but his content took him all over Europe and the USA and it was completely non-existent in the UK. We&#8217;d meet up and I&#8217;d talk to him or her all over again in his or her native language.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/one-thing-that-never-changes-about-online-marketing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hey, Writer!</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/hey-writer/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/hey-writer/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 09:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Good Reads]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Worldwide]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=315</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Yes, Your&#8217;re A Great Writer. Yes, you&#8217;re a great writer. And you deserve to make a great living from writing articles, right? But maybe you don’t know what to do next to reach your goals. Do you sometimes feel confused and overwhelmed? Like you’re spinning your wheels and not getting traction? It&#8217;s ok; you&#8217;re not [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h6>Yes, Your&#8217;re A Great Writer.</h6>



<p>Yes, you&#8217;re a great writer. And you deserve to make a great living from writing articles, right? But maybe you don’t know what to do next to reach your goals. Do you sometimes feel confused and overwhelmed? Like you’re spinning your wheels and not getting traction?</p>



<p>It&#8217;s ok; you&#8217;re not alone.</p>



<p>That was pretty much it for the conversation. I could just tell we had a lot of similarities in how we approached our work, but I still liked that he wasn&#8217;t expecting it. </p>



<p>As he later admitted to me afterwards, I had a lot of my feelings towards him hurt on this occasion. I&#8217;m not really one to argue with his opinions; I really respect the work he does and I believe he has a lot of his passion out for writing and having a voice within the industry when it comes to his vision.</p>



<p>Nevertheless, he and he are close friends, which is why I had no issue taking to heart what I saw as a somewhat obvious comment that he made to me.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/hey-writer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Travel the World and Get Companies to Pay For It.</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/how-to-travel-the-world-and-get-companies-to-pay-for-it/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/how-to-travel-the-world-and-get-companies-to-pay-for-it/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 09:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Worldwide]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=299</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Don’t get excited, it doesn’t work like that. That&#8217;s the challenge behind the new Startup Europe: how to turn some of the world&#8217;s biggest companies and startups into real, lasting businesses that help us all thrive. What they find is that if you set a low standard for what an average company or startup can [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h6>Don’t get excited, it doesn’t work like that.</h6>



<p>That&#8217;s the challenge behind the new Startup Europe: how to turn some of the world&#8217;s biggest companies and startups into real, lasting businesses that help us all thrive.</p>



<p>What they find is that if you set a low standard for what an average company or startup can and should do, that starts to shift the culture of those around you.</p>



<hr class="wp-block-separator is-style-dots"/>



<p>The best examples are Airbnb, the home sharing app, and Google, the search engine company.</p>



<p>The startups, which are backed by Silicon Valley firms such as Intel, and often have offices in their homes, have built businesses that, like Airbnb, they say make the world a better place for everyone.</p>



<p>Airbnb has grown from three workers to 15, and has made an impact around the world. Now, as the Silicon Valley version of the startup boom grinds to a close, many worry that the good guys will win — though the reality is there are many more who simply don&#8217;t know how to scale.</p>



<hr class="wp-block-separator is-style-dots"/>



<p>Here, we&#8217;ve laid out eight key steps to creating companies that help you become the world&#8217;s most valuable company in five years or less.</p>



<p>I started investing in this business the day the Wall Street Journal ran a series on me, and this is how I started and I have stayed for five, six years and for that I am extremely grateful. My financial performance has been absolutely consistent. If you ask, how I could do it all for you, I could not answer. I have worked hard and I have kept my work ethic and how I perform.</p>



<hr class="wp-block-separator is-style-dots"/>



<p>How to use a little common sense when making decisions: If you are going in with a long-term intention, you will always look at everything through an objective but if in fact everything comes down to the money and that is what matters, you probably should listen to the people around you and if you are willing to sacrifice a little bit you will still get the results.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/how-to-travel-the-world-and-get-companies-to-pay-for-it/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Making Music, Spreading Smiles</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/673-2/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/673-2/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mangusta Rust]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 14:58:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Worldwide]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Audio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Worlwide]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=673</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Music by Max Sergeev from Fugue Artists, art lovers and art lovers alike are inspired by the new Mondo event, a celebration of visual art, storytelling and music. It gives an opportunity for art lovers across the country to learn more about the culture they love, and to enjoy the artists playing, the artists promoting [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Music by <a href="https://icons8.com/music/author/max-sergeev">Max Sergeev</a> from <a href="/music">Fugue</a></p>



<p>Artists, art lovers and art lovers alike are inspired by the new Mondo event, a celebration of visual art, storytelling and music. It gives an opportunity for art lovers across the country to learn more about the culture they love, and to enjoy the artists playing, the artists promoting and the artists that will have a part in the festivities.</p>



<iframe width="100%" height="166" scrolling="no" frameborder="no" allow="autoplay" src="https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/8150343&#038;color=%23f0917a&#038;auto_play=false&#038;hide_related=false&#038;show_comments=true&#038;show_user=true&#038;show_reposts=false&#038;show_teaser=true"></iframe>



<p>The Mondo Music Festival will continue to bring diverse voices from around the country to San Antonio at a weekend that will include an art gallery in historic Frank Lloyd Wright Park, live music and workshops.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/673-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
