<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Travel &#8211; Publisher</title>
	<atom:link href="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/tag/travel/feed/?layout=boxed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher</link>
	<description>Publishing platform template for Wordpress</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 15:12:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.4</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Travel &#8211; Publisher</title>
	<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Neon Metropolis: Your city in fantasy</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/modern-metropolis-your-city-in-fantasy/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/modern-metropolis-your-city-in-fantasy/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Gabriel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 15:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Worldwide]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Worlwide]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=457</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Metropolis is indeed an ancient city, but this would not explain why it looks like a city of a million square feet, and not another of the great ancient cities of Greek or Roman antiquity. There are many theories for what caused this. For instance, there was an event known as the fall of [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-drop-cap">The Metropolis is indeed an ancient city, but this would not explain why it looks like a city of a million square feet, and not another of the great ancient cities of Greek or Roman antiquity. There are many theories for what caused this. For instance, there was an event known as the fall of Atlantis that happened somewhere between the second century BCE and the fourth century CE.</p>



<p>What do we find in all this ancient knowledge? Most Greek and Roman monuments are much less complex and, in many cases, almost impossible to identify. The Metropolis is a monument that dates to the middle ages. It is a great stone monument of the Iron Age, an ancient city built in the form of a walled district. The ancient Greek writers were far more detailed with the monuments they created and did not only discuss the nature of the walls, but they spoke about a great many other buildings of this great civilization. I will mention just one of the other famous monuments, the great pyramid or pyramids built by the Sumerians. This great pyramid, known as the Great Pyramid, is in Iraq, and was located on the south side of the mountain known as Mount Sinir.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/modern-metropolis-your-city-in-fantasy/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Be a Specialist in Traveling with Your Mountain Bike</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/be-a-specialist-in-traveling-with-your-mountain-bike/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/be-a-specialist-in-traveling-with-your-mountain-bike/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 13:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bikes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Flat design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mountain]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=403</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Go to the Biking School! (This school is just down the hall from The Bicycle School.) Get our guide to getting to the University of Waterloo and get a sense of where to go to get the best transportation possible. We are also looking for volunteers. If we have room to hire additional staff to [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-drop-cap">Go to the Biking School! (This school is just down the hall from The Bicycle School.) Get our guide to getting to the University of Waterloo and get a sense of where to go to get the best transportation possible.</p>



<p>We are also looking for volunteers. If we have room to hire additional staff to help with the website, we might. Volunteers are essential for keeping the site running, updating the curriculum, and making this site accessible to everyone.</p>



<p>If you&#8217;re traveling with a bike we highly recommend that you take time out of your daily routine to travel together with me, because they&#8217;re the lifeblood of my business and the people who rely on them every day.</p>



<div class="wp-block-svq-block-gallery svq-gallery-grid svq-gallery--view-4"><div class="svq-gallery__item"><div class="svq-gallery__image-wrapp" data-more="-1"><a class="svq-gallery__image-link" href="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/56515.min_.png" data-fancybox="gallery"><img class="svq-gallery__image wp-image-862" data-src="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/56515.min_.png" data-progressive-sm="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/56515.min_.png" src="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/56515.min_.png" alt="" data-id="862" data-object-fit="cover" srcset="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/56515.min_.png 800w, https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/56515.min_-300x268.png 300w, https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/56515.min_-768x686.png 768w, https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/56515.min_-45x40.png 45w" sizes="(min-width: 960px) 75vw, 100vw" /></a></div></div><div class="svq-gallery__item"><div class="svq-gallery__image-wrapp" data-more="-1"><a class="svq-gallery__image-link" href="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/2253697.min_-753x1024.png" data-fancybox="gallery"><img class="svq-gallery__image wp-image-858" data-src="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/2253697.min_-753x1024.png" data-progressive-sm="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/2253697.min_-753x1024.png" src="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/2253697.min_-753x1024.png" alt="" data-id="858" data-object-fit="cover"/></a></div></div><div class="svq-gallery__item"><div class="svq-gallery__image-wrapp" data-more="-1"><a class="svq-gallery__image-link" href="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/56512.png" data-fancybox="gallery"><img class="svq-gallery__image wp-image-861" data-src="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/56512.png" data-progressive-sm="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/56512.png" src="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/56512.png" alt="" data-id="861" data-object-fit="cover"/></a></div></div><div class="svq-gallery__item"><div class="svq-gallery__image-wrapp" data-more="-1"><a class="svq-gallery__image-link" href="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/8856.min_.png" data-fancybox="gallery"><img class="svq-gallery__image wp-image-860" data-src="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/8856.min_.png" data-progressive-sm="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/8856.min_.png" src="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/8856.min_.png" alt="" data-id="860" data-object-fit="cover"/></a></div></div></div>



<p>In the past we have had some great members from New Zealand coming for the course, in a couple of years we are expecting even more! More importantly we are looking for members from all over. As soon as possible, if you have already booked a time, we will get in touch.</p>



<p>Please note that the class is for general use, however each member can complete various sections of the curriculum while travelling with their Mountain Bike. We encourage you to bring along an extra bike to complete the course, as they can be of use, particularly if your bike has already been checked out/checked out and is still not ready for mountain biking.</p>



<p>During this stage we want to keep it simple, and focus on the basic techniques found in mountain biking, but it&#8217;s an exciting time to be riding the bike.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/be-a-specialist-in-traveling-with-your-mountain-bike/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Travel the World and Get Companies to Pay For It.</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/how-to-travel-the-world-and-get-companies-to-pay-for-it/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/how-to-travel-the-world-and-get-companies-to-pay-for-it/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 09:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Worldwide]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=299</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Don’t get excited, it doesn’t work like that. That&#8217;s the challenge behind the new Startup Europe: how to turn some of the world&#8217;s biggest companies and startups into real, lasting businesses that help us all thrive. What they find is that if you set a low standard for what an average company or startup can [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h6>Don’t get excited, it doesn’t work like that.</h6>



<p>That&#8217;s the challenge behind the new Startup Europe: how to turn some of the world&#8217;s biggest companies and startups into real, lasting businesses that help us all thrive.</p>



<p>What they find is that if you set a low standard for what an average company or startup can and should do, that starts to shift the culture of those around you.</p>



<hr class="wp-block-separator is-style-dots"/>



<p>The best examples are Airbnb, the home sharing app, and Google, the search engine company.</p>



<p>The startups, which are backed by Silicon Valley firms such as Intel, and often have offices in their homes, have built businesses that, like Airbnb, they say make the world a better place for everyone.</p>



<p>Airbnb has grown from three workers to 15, and has made an impact around the world. Now, as the Silicon Valley version of the startup boom grinds to a close, many worry that the good guys will win — though the reality is there are many more who simply don&#8217;t know how to scale.</p>



<hr class="wp-block-separator is-style-dots"/>



<p>Here, we&#8217;ve laid out eight key steps to creating companies that help you become the world&#8217;s most valuable company in five years or less.</p>



<p>I started investing in this business the day the Wall Street Journal ran a series on me, and this is how I started and I have stayed for five, six years and for that I am extremely grateful. My financial performance has been absolutely consistent. If you ask, how I could do it all for you, I could not answer. I have worked hard and I have kept my work ethic and how I perform.</p>



<hr class="wp-block-separator is-style-dots"/>



<p>How to use a little common sense when making decisions: If you are going in with a long-term intention, you will always look at everything through an objective but if in fact everything comes down to the money and that is what matters, you probably should listen to the people around you and if you are willing to sacrifice a little bit you will still get the results.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/how-to-travel-the-world-and-get-companies-to-pay-for-it/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Going to the Moon</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/going-to-the-moon/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/going-to-the-moon/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 09:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=41</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[My first travel to moon was a successful journey. After completing the mission, I had two of my favorite activities planned out ahead of time: walking along the beach of the beach in Hawaii, and getting my photo taken with the lunar craters. I&#8217;ve also always liked to spend time with my wife and I [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-drop-cap">My first travel to moon was a successful journey. After completing the mission, I had two of my favorite activities planned out ahead of time: walking along the beach of the beach in Hawaii, and getting my photo taken with the lunar craters. I&#8217;ve also always liked to spend time with my wife and I with walks, swims, and picnics. The time spent in these activities was always very relaxing, and very enjoyable.</p>



<p>I went to space at age 12. Before any of the kids went to space, it was very exciting and surreal to tell them the news — that we were going to go. That really shaped my thinking about where we&#8217;d set up and what kind of future we were having. We wanted them to go to school and get college degrees, so when I went to space — when there were no other options! — it opened up so many options both in terms of how we were going to live and learn!</p>



<p>I wanted those kids to do amazing things, whether it was working in space, being involved in politics, or studying the sciences. The idea that there might be an alternative to these major career paths? That seemed important to me. The time I spent in space, on the moon, and the experiences with me and my wife — it changed my life. I loved exploring, learning, and enjoying life. I think that I&#8217;d be better off</p>



<p>I have been travelling for years since. I do not want to stop because it is very difficult for me now to meet people on moon. I had to learn many things and understand many things.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-style-large"><p>Some of those things I can understand because Moon is not much more than a light.</p></blockquote>



<p>&nbsp;I met many people and learned from them a lot, but some of my best friends at first. I started to fall in love with them and decided to meet them again. I did not need to study them to understand them and I didn&#8217;t want to. I just wanted to make friends with them and have a good time on Moon. It is quite easy to forget that.</p>



<p>To be honest the hardest part about going to the moon was the distance. It&#8217;s hard to keep up with the movements of the moon for days at a time, which would make us stay up at night and eat a lot of calories while our bodies are tired. In my first month on it, I was at 12,000 meters and about 5-7 hours behind, although my legs were going strong after 3 days of going that far. In the beginning, I didn&#8217;t know how to use my legs.</p>



<p>Now I know well how to use them all. There is no pain and no sleep.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/going-to-the-moon/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
