<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Technology &#8211; Publisher</title>
	<atom:link href="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/tag/technology/feed/?layout=boxed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher</link>
	<description>Publishing platform template for Wordpress</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 15:27:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.4</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Technology &#8211; Publisher</title>
	<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Technology Is Growing Fast and Changing Our Lives Essay</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/technology-is-growing-fast-and-changing-our-lives-essay/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/technology-is-growing-fast-and-changing-our-lives-essay/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 10:37:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=240</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The new technology revolution is creating tremendous value for businesses across the economic spectrum. With so much information technology available that enables millions of companies and professionals to reach new levels of success, it is no wonder how much consumers spend. According to a recent Pew Research Center report, about 25.2% of consumers spend at [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>The new technology revolution</strong> is creating tremendous value for businesses across the economic spectrum.</p>



<p>With so much information technology available that enables millions of companies and professionals to reach new levels of success, it is no wonder how much consumers spend. According to a recent Pew Research Center report, about 25.2% of consumers spend at least some of their purchases online.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><img src="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/undraw_mobile_user_7oqo.min_-1024x618.png" alt="" class="wp-image-610"/></figure>



<blockquote style="text-align:center" class="wp-block-quote is-style-large"><p>Knowledge without action is meaningless.</p><cite>Abu Bakr</cite></blockquote>



<p>Now, with so many choices to choose from, there is always room to expand your business marketing strategy and increase conversions.</p>



<p>If you&#8217;re like most businesses, your sales team has a role in maximizing your business&#8217; ROI and expanding your reach.</p>



<p>The most important step in marketing and promoting your business is developing compelling and creative marketing and promotional materials.</p>



<div class="wp-block-image is-floated"><figure class="alignright"><img src="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/undraw_version_control_9bpv-1024x684.png" alt="" class="wp-image-252"/></figure></div>



<p>Research, write and edit professional business promotional materials in order to create compelling materials that will help your business stand out from the competition. The marketing department will also work with your sales staff to create customized materials where you can add value to your business.</p>



<p>Prove to yourself that the right promotional material will help your company stand out from the competition. Start by studying the top 20 most successful businesses and finding a number of examples that best explain how they did it and explain what the sales team and the marketing department accomplished with them</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/technology-is-growing-fast-and-changing-our-lives-essay/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Becoming a Virtual Reality Designer</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/becoming-a-virtual-reality-designer/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/becoming-a-virtual-reality-designer/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 13:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Virtual Reality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=621</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As VR technology is evolving, it is challenging for designers to use it effectively. Even with years of experience, many traditional design professionals feel stuck, unable to push the limits of immersion, and not able to create virtual prototypes of what they want. In fact, a lot of these conventional industry professionals feel like the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-drop-cap">As VR technology is evolving, it is challenging for designers to use it effectively. Even with years of experience, many traditional design professionals feel stuck, unable to push the limits of immersion, and not able to create virtual prototypes of what they want. In fact, a lot of these conventional industry professionals feel like the technology is &#8220;too big&#8221; and not sufficiently accessible. This leaves us with designers who feel that it is just not possible, because the technology is so abstract or difficult to understand. This disconnect is becoming increasingly apparent in industry.</p>



<div class="wp-block-image is-floated"><figure class="alignright"><img src="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/1629.min_.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-634"/></figure></div>



<p>One common experience of VR developer is the disappointment of being unable to deliver a prototype and learn from it.</p>



<p>The process starts when you start exploring more abstract possibilities with virtual reality. From that start the concept of a &#8220;prototype&#8221; gets abstracted from you and becomes another term for something that is merely a &#8220;proof of concept&#8221;. The concept of an &#8220;actual&#8221; prototype becomes less and less important to you as you move further away from the goal. Your &#8220;pros to learn from&#8221; starts to become meaningless.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p><strong>Becoming a Virtual Reality Designer</strong>&nbsp;is not easy. However the skill that you need to learn can easily be learned even easily.<br></p></blockquote>



<p>I am no different. I worked as a software engineer for many years, and learned many techniques. Now, as a virtual reality designer and web developer, I have grown up with tools which are easily accessible to me, and the knowledge I can gain from developing these types of applications for virtual reality. Therefore I have dedicated myself to learning other virtual reality technologies and tools over the next year or so.</p>



<div class="wp-block-image is-floated"><figure class="alignleft"><img src="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/vr-glasses.min_-1024x527.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-637"/></figure></div>



<p>Here is an example of what I am currently learning. I recently attended the 3rd VR World Congress (VRWorlds) from January 11th to 28th, 2016. I had a chance to speak with a number of interesting developers who were passionate about VR and VR-related topics. </p>



<p>We had a fascinating time, and one of the things I learned is that while virtual reality is growing, there still needs to be dedicated resources for it. While most of our community are currently focused on building VR demos and training for VR players, there is still a large amount of work to be done.</p>



<p>So I have focused my efforts on creating dedicated resources for virtual reality in general and for VR games specifically for all platforms.</p>



<p>There are various forums and community groups, forums, and forum support programs online, but there still needs to be dedicated dedicated resources dedicated to virtual reality for PC</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/becoming-a-virtual-reality-designer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to easily do Object Detection on Drone Imagery using Deep learning</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/how-to-easily-do-object-detection-on-drone-imagery-using-deep-learning/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/how-to-easily-do-object-detection-on-drone-imagery-using-deep-learning/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 09:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Drone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tutorials]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=516</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There are also ways to easily detect objects in complex programs without even doing the object detection yourself. For example, to detect arrays, you have to know exactly what values they contain (this will be explained in more detail later). How to easily do Object Detection with Javacsript Consider the following JavaScript code. The variable [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-drop-cap">There are also ways to easily detect objects in complex programs without even doing the object detection yourself. For example, to detect arrays, you have to know exactly what values they contain (this will be explained in more detail later).</p>



<h4><strong>How to easily do Object Detection with Javacsript</strong></h4>



<p>Consider the following JavaScript code. The variable name contains 2 items (i.e. a comma-separated array). A user can check the number of items inside of the array by writing &#8220;foo&#8221; as &#8220;1,2,3&#8221;;</p>



<pre class="wp-block-preformatted wp-block-svq-code prettyprint">var array = [1] + "Baz";
var foo = [1,2];
for (var i = 1; i &lt;= array.length; i++) {
foo[i] = 5;
}</pre>



<div class="wp-block-image is-floated"><figure class="alignleft"><img src="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/548.min_.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-541"/></figure></div>



<p>A few years ago I worked on a new project called Signal Detection and Recognition, which uses an X-Ray image acquired during spaceflight to identify spacecraft.</p>



<p>I wrote that implementation in C and then ran the program against it using gdb.</p>



<p>In this post we will explain how that was done. You can read my prior post about the implementation here; if you enjoy this blog, we can also discuss the new feature in Go here or the upcoming rewrite of X-Ray to work better with Go.</p>



<p>Now let&#8217;s dive into the very easy part of Object <sup class="svq-sidelink" data-svq-note="3"><a href="javascript:void(0)" >3</a></sup><span class="svq-sidenote will-animate" data-cssanimate="fadeIn" data-svq-note="3">Object-oriented programming(OOP) is aprogramming paradigm based on the concept of &#8220;objects&#8221;, which can contain data, in the form of fields, and code, in the form ofprocedures (often known as methotds).</span> detection with us. We will learn how one uses the Javacript language to understand some common constructs.</p>



<p>This includes understanding the syntax of some common patterns and patterns like the return types of Javacript and how to generate a class of some class. Before we step away from Javacript though, here is your first piece of Java Object detection with us.</p>



<h6>OCR Function:</h6>



<pre class="wp-block-preformatted wp-block-svq-code prettyprint">recognitionImageElement.addEventListener('change', () =&gt; {
 if (!recognitionImageElement.files) {
   return null;
 }
const file = recognitionImageElement.files[0];
})</pre>



<h6>Dealing with the&nbsp;result:</h6>



<p>The result of the <code>.recognition()</code> method <sup class="svq-sidelink" data-svq-note="4"><a href="javascript:void(0)" >4</a></sup><span class="svq-sidenote will-animate" data-cssanimate="fadeIn" data-svq-note="4">A method in object-oriented programming (OOP) is a procedure asociated with a message and an object. An object consists of data and behavior. The data and behavior comprise an interface, which specifies how the object may be utilized by any of various consumers of the object.</span> is confusing, to say the least. It is not well documented and so we have to deduce some things on our own:</p>



<pre class="wp-block-preformatted wp-block-svq-code prettyprint">{
    blocks: Array[1]
    confidence: 87
    html: "&lt;div class='ocr_page' id='page_1' ..."
    lines: Array[3]
    oem: "DEFAULT"
    paragraphs: Array[1]
    psm: "SINGLE_BLOCK"
    symbols: Array[33]
    text: "Hello World↵from beyond↵the Cosmic Void↵↵"
    version: "3.04.00"
    words: Array[7]
}</pre>



<h6>Conclusion</h6>



<p>The Javascript library provides us with a ready-to-use OCR implementation that is efficient and, for the most part, accurate. The additional advantage of the library is its immense flexibility thanks to being compatible with both Node.js and a browser. There is even an option to include custom training data which could make it work better for your specific applications.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/how-to-easily-do-object-detection-on-drone-imagery-using-deep-learning/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>5</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Rise of Type Design</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/flat-design-and-the-rise-of-type-design/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/flat-design-and-the-rise-of-type-design/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 09:43:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Flat design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Graphics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=371</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[When the designers of Flat Design created their first prototype of the typeface, they had one simple goal, which was to create a universal, attractive and memorable typeface. They wanted to create both a style and a typefaces – something which had no specific name, like &#8216;L&#8217; in the French capital. These are all well [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-drop-cap">When the designers of Flat Design created their first prototype of the typeface, they had one simple goal, which was to create a universal, attractive and memorable typeface. They wanted to create both a style and a typefaces – something which had no specific name, like &#8216;L&#8217; in the French capital. These are all well established rules that designers follow when they have a project in mind like this, but for Flat, it was a lot more complex and they had no idea how to do it. The typefaces to be the basis of their flat design philosophy was very much on their own minds, especially the two that they chose.</p>



<p>With all it&#8217;s features, Flat Design was the creation of four people; Martin, Martin Martinovich, Martin Reindl, and Paul Reindl. Martin gave his sidenote Rails display optional accompanying content outside of the main viewport of your website. <sq-note>Sites often use sidenotes content to fix additional often optional content to your viewport as you scroll through the page.</sq-note> content and helped with the design by using his personal experience as an artist in Paris.</p>



<p>He also gave away a lot of feedback during the design process, which helped shape the new project of Flat Design. The most important thing Martin asked for was consistency; as he always tried to use typefaces with subtle contrasts to distinguish them from each other. With his experience, Martin wanted to make a new design in response to his own needs, which led to the addition of three unique designs.</p>



<div class="wp-block-image is-floated"><figure class="alignleft"><img src="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/56515.min_.png" alt="" class="wp-image-862" srcset="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/56515.min_.png 800w, https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/56515.min_-300x268.png 300w, https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/56515.min_-768x686.png 768w, https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/56515.min_-45x40.png 45w" sizes="(min-width: 960px) 75vw, 100vw" /></figure></div>



<p>In a recent interview with Wired, the inventor of the flat design, Peter Thiel, talked more about his theory of why the flat shape works and what you can do to create a flat design.</p>



<p>I think a flat design is very, very important because it helps us to understand that the shape and the way we think about shapes, shapes and their functions are so strongly interconnected. We&#8217;re very, very influenced by each other, but also deeply connected. What we&#8217;re going against is that we try to do a lot of things with a flat design that&#8217;s going to create a lot of pain and we&#8217;re doing that by having very different approaches to what shape should be.</p>



<p>And what we have in the past is very simplistic.</p>



<p>There&#8217;s a really big assumption that we make that we&#8217;re going to get rid of all the things but the form of the design is more important than these things. You get rid of these forms and you get rid of this form of form, and that can make this thing seem rigid because you&#8217;re putting more emphasis on that shape and this other form that&#8217;s completely abstract and abstract.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/flat-design-and-the-rise-of-type-design/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>4</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
