<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Lifestyle &#8211; Publisher</title>
	<atom:link href="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/tag/lifestyle/feed/?layout=boxed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher</link>
	<description>Publishing platform template for Wordpress</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 11:28:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.4</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Lifestyle &#8211; Publisher</title>
	<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>What is an Influencer?</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/what-is-an-influencer/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/what-is-an-influencer/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mangusta Rust]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 08:37:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Worldwide]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Productivity]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/?p=982</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[An influencer is someone who has a large following within the product or service, and can influence customers or potential customers to take a particular action. I&#8217;ve written before about how the &#8220;social media manager&#8221; is key to building a successful product, and why influencers are key to building strong brand authority as well. How [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-drop-cap">An influencer is someone who has a large following within the product or service, and can influence customers or potential customers to take a particular action.</p>



<p>I&#8217;ve written before about how the &#8220;social media manager&#8221; is key to building a successful product, and why influencers are key to building strong brand authority as well.</p>



<p>How do you build influencers? Here is the process:</p>



<p>Create a goal – Set a target audience and set the goal. Use social media platforms to gather this &#8220;know your consumer&#8221; information. Determine the right people to target. Look to identify influencers you know that have a strong following on each channel, and use them to help you reach those customers. Invite the influencers you&#8217;ve identified to be part of your product, or product launch.</p>



<p>This process will help you create strong relationships with influencers using social media. By following my advice, you can build strong influence within a short amount of time.</p>



<h4>How to Find An Influencer?</h4>



<p>One of the best ways to find an influencers online is to find them on social media and on social networks like Facebook and Twitter.</p>



<p>For example, here are some of their sites/websites that would make an excellent candidate as part of your online outreach:</p>



<h6><strong>Instagram</strong></h6>



<p>Instagram offers several good ways to get involved with Instagram or any other social network.</p>



<p>Follow the Instagram Community on social media sites like Twitter and Facebook.</p>



<p>Follow the Instagram community on Instagram to find influencers who have a particular niche in Instagram and the influencers will usually post their photos to their social media accounts, as well.</p>



<p>Follow the Instagram Community to help them promote your Instagram products / services.</p>



<p>If you want to learn how to become featured in Instagram then head to this Instagram website and sign-up for the Instagram Insider Program.</p>



<h6><strong>Facebook</strong></h6>



<p>Facebook is the main social networking site by a country mile. Therefore, it has an incredible amount of potential.<br></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/what-is-an-influencer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>3</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
