<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Goodreads &#8211; Publisher</title>
	<atom:link href="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/tag/goodreads/feed/?layout=boxed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher</link>
	<description>Publishing platform template for Wordpress</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 15:27:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.4</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Goodreads &#8211; Publisher</title>
	<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Happy News!</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/happy-news/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/happy-news/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 15:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Good Reads]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Goodreads]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=140</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A new subscription offer  has just been announced with all new deals being coming early in the future. I hope you enjoyed the blog as much as I enjoyed contributing to it. As always feel free to reach out via social media any feedback, critiques or suggestions you might have. As always this blog is dedicated to my [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-drop-cap">A new subscription offer  has just been announced with all new deals being coming early in the future. I hope you enjoyed the blog as much as I enjoyed contributing to it. As always feel free to reach out via social media any feedback, critiques or suggestions you might have. As always this blog is dedicated to my friend and fellow Bryan.  Thank you for reading, and I look forward to talking about you all more in the future.</p>



<p>I hope you enjoyed the blog as much as I enjoyed contributing to it. As always feel free to reach out via social media any feedback, critiques or suggestions you might have. As always this blog is dedicated to my friend and fellow&nbsp;Bryan. &nbsp;Thank you for reading, and I look forward to talking about you all more in the future.</p>



<p>Today&#8217;s topic is &#8220;what is the best and worst thing you have to do to stay motivated?&#8221; I found a list that I just wanted to share, so let&#8217;s get started!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><img src="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/undraw_happy_news_hxmt-1024x675.png" alt="" class="wp-image-142"/></figure>



<h4>The Benefits Of Keeping Motivation In Your Head</h4>



<p>For anyone who likes to try new things in order to learn, think, and be inspired, writing a new book or blog post would mean the world to me, and I&#8217;m hoping you will too. For those of you who are currently in the middle of writing something new and want to get inspired or improve on ideas you already have, I think you can start by creating an old blog post that summarizes your motivation from the beginning of your journey.</p>



<hr class="wp-block-separator is-style-dots"/>



<p>This helps you start a fresh narrative from the beginning, and you&#8217;ll then be able to keep going without looking forward to &#8220;the day (after) it actually happened.&#8221; When you&#8217;re at that crossroad in your life, keeping your motivation is key because now you have something concrete to lean on, a new way to look at your current situation.</p>



<p>It&#8217;s important to keep in mind where you started. When I first started blogging, there were no tools like Google Sheets or Google Docs.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/happy-news/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Don&#8217;t Get Lost, Be Productive</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/dont-get-lost-be-productive/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/dont-get-lost-be-productive/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 16:21:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Good Reads]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Goodreads]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=719</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The most common reason a person may lose an eye is lack of focus. However, it can also occur when a person becomes distracted. As you become more aware of what is going on around you, you will be able to avoid this type of problem because you have noticed when your eyes are wandering [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-drop-cap">The most common reason a person may lose an eye is lack of focus. However, it can also occur when a person becomes distracted. As you become more aware of what is going on around you, you will be able to avoid this type of problem because you have noticed when your eyes are wandering or wandering in the wrong direction that you are causing distractions. This type of problem is more easily avoided if those on your team look out for the eye movement and focus in on it.</p>



<p>Another common reason a person may lose an eye from lack of focus is in a crowded environment and is often brought on themselves by their friends. You will never see the person who is having a bad day when it ends up getting the eye.</p>



<p>The average number of hours a man spends on a job, based on government data on the distribution of workers throughout the economy, has dropped substantially over the last 45 years.</p>



<p>The chart below, which is based on a study by economists from Boston College, the University of Massachusetts and the University of Michigan, shows how hours worked have changed in the U.S. since 1976. The percentage of working women per hour has dropped steadily from 12.2% to 6.6% since 1976. Over this period the total total hours worked has declined by nearly one half, from 1.3 trillion hours to 1.2 trillion hours since 1976.</p>



<p>Men&#8217;s average amount of total work hours has also declined, from 2.5 hours to 2.7 hours per hour over the same period. This is likely due to the fact that they are now working on average 741 hours a week, about 60 percent of their 1972 peak.</p>



<p>Communication is one of the most essential and essential components of any team. When communicating issues, the most important thing is to clearly understand what has happened. You must ensure that your communication is accurate because if you do not, the issue will remain unresolved.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/dont-get-lost-be-productive/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Running on The Road &#8211; A Self Hosted Video</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/running-on-the-road/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/running-on-the-road/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 14:48:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Video Tutorials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Goodreads]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=441</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[My One-Night Stand with a Butterfly&#8216; is probably my favorite album of 2014. A song that&#8217;s only accessible to people who know one of its lyrics. I&#8217;m sure that&#8217;s all true… but it&#8217;s also an example of how things change. The music and the lyrics will always change. We have to move, and we have [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>My One-Night Stand with a Butterfly</strong>&#8216; is probably my favorite album of 2014. A song that&#8217;s only accessible to people who know one of its lyrics.</p>



<p>I&#8217;m sure that&#8217;s all true… but it&#8217;s also an example of how things change. The music and the lyrics will always change.</p>



<p>We have to move, and we have to change. So will we have to move away from this country, to something that&#8217;s completely foreign, not even from our own family, but from the one I was raised in? That&#8217;s the question we&#8217;re asking now, and I think we&#8217;re probably in a pretty dangerous position to just keep talking about, which doesn&#8217;t make it all okay… to talk about, which doesn&#8217;t make us okay…</p>



<p>I&#8217;ve heard that it is.</p>



<p>Now that we know our country, and the things we feel are here, and this country isn&#8217;t the last to be colonized, I wonder how much of this has happened over the years, what it said about us, where our values, our values are relative to these other countries. I wonder how that makes it seem.</p>



<p>It&#8217;s not about sex, drugs or rock &#8216;n&#8217; roll; it&#8217;s about art, love, family, friendship, art and a simple concept: the beauty inside of a human. I&#8217;ve gotten lots of email from artists wanting to collaborate or just collaborate with me, but there is a reason that this particular one has got so many more readers. The reason is because of my &#8220;Betta Fish.&#8221;</p>



<p>The concept is simple. It&#8217;s about how our relationships affect our health. To me, that doesn&#8217;t even have to be art. I love how everyone around me talks about their love of art, but nothing has a chance to work without having an impact if it is simply an individual interaction – that is just a one-night stand. My song &#8216;Moms at Work&#8217; is about one such encounter. &#8220;I met my best friend (on my Betta Fish&#8221;). He&#8217;s my best friend, but he&#8217;ll never tell me the difference because he always thought of me as my &#8216;boyfriend&#8217;.&#8221;</p>



<p>That&#8217;s the essence of &#8216;Betta Fish.&#8217; He knew a lot more than he thought he did, and he loved me for being me and not trying to be more, without feeling like he was controlling the person he was with.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/running-on-the-road/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>One Thing That Never Changes About Online Marketing</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/one-thing-that-never-changes-about-online-marketing/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/one-thing-that-never-changes-about-online-marketing/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 14:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Worldwide]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Goodreads]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=432</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[So what exactly was so hard about &#8220;Not Your Business&#8221;? The bottom line: If you&#8217;re a small business looking to grow online, it&#8217;s tough. It takes a lot of resources, effort and money. In fact, your success will be measured by whether you can get your content delivered on time — as opposed to just [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>So what exactly was so hard about &#8220;Not Your Business&#8221;? The bottom line: If you&#8217;re a small business looking to grow online, it&#8217;s tough. It takes a lot of resources, effort and money. In fact, your success will be measured by whether you can get your content delivered on time — as opposed to just getting it through your &#8220;recreational&#8221; business — even once you&#8217;ve created your business (remember all the times you say you don&#8217;t want to make money?).</p>



<p>You may be thinking that&#8217;s because you&#8217;re not making money, so the idea is ridiculous. That said, one thing that never changes is that it&#8217;s hard to stay out of your own little bubble.</p>



<p>At one point a friend of mine who was a graphic designer just started a blog named &#8220;How To Make A Living Online.&#8221; He was a big time content creator, but his content took him all over Europe and the USA and it was completely non-existent in the UK. We&#8217;d meet up and I&#8217;d talk to him or her all over again in his or her native language.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/one-thing-that-never-changes-about-online-marketing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sunrise and Sunset on Mars</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/sunrise-and-sunset-on-mars/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/sunrise-and-sunset-on-mars/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mangusta Rust]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 09:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Good Reads]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Goodreads]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=392</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To explore the surface of Mars as a whole, scientists have focused almost exclusively on a portion of its surface, called the &#8216;Celestial latitudes&#8217;. It has a latitude of about 55 degrees north, and a longitude of about 2 degrees south. The surface is cold at this latitude, and at a very specific location, in [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-drop-cap"><strong>To explore the surface of Mars</strong> as a whole, scientists have focused almost exclusively on a portion of its surface, called the &#8216;Celestial latitudes&#8217;. It has a latitude of about 55 degrees north, and a longitude of about 2 degrees south. The surface is cold at this latitude, and at a very specific location, in a crater-filled region called the Meridiani Planum, where Earth is closest to Mars.</p>



<p>When we look at the evening sky over Mars, we usually see the same sky over a variety of different views.</p>



<p>The Sun makes an appearance, but a combination of small dust grains and dust storms is visible. During Mars&#8217; annual winter, it is a little brighter than the rest of the planet, making it difficult to capture with a small telescope.</p>



<p>On average, the Sun appears as a little reddish-orange due to dust in the atmosphere.</p>



<p>For this Martian year, I will likely look up at a clear night, with a couple of dark spotlights on a tripod or small telescope at about 7:30 pm. For several hours, I will observe the bright Sun rise, and then return to the same spotlight at twilight. From the moonlit mountain pass above the pass, I will then look down into a valley, and then up into the pass.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/sunrise-and-sunset-on-mars/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Car is Alive!</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/this-car-is-alive/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/this-car-is-alive/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 15:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Good Reads]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Video]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Goodreads]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=465</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The car itself is replaced with a brand new, working model. A car we have been building before because it is a tool. A tool that works a lot better than we imagined it to work in the past or even in our dreams. It&#8217;s a way to get our daily fix of driving the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The car itself is replaced with a brand new, working model. A car we have been building before because it is a tool. A tool that works a lot better than we imagined it to work in the past or even in our dreams.</p>



<p>It&#8217;s a way to get our daily fix of driving the same motor we have been making for nearly thirty years, just to see how it turns out. The car itself is a nice, quiet little machine that we can drive around and enjoy for hours on end without worrying about the engine, gears or anything else, and then, to add to that, it has a lot of fun while it&#8217;s charging.</p>



<p><strong>BMW Car Manufactory</strong>&nbsp;(Daimler AG) confirmed it had signed a £500 million contract for the new generation BMW 7 Series. &#8220;This agreement will help us bring in more innovative models and products that will appeal to and satisfy the high-volume customers who are enjoying our range of new models and we are already meeting with a number of other manufacturers&#8221;.</p>



<p>The firm has also signed an agreement with McLaren to produce a car in future. To date there has been very little news on how this deal would work out, although the deal with McLaren appears to be aimed at helping McLaren develop the new 7 Series car from within the BMW Group.</p>



<p>According to the report, BMW had offered &#8216;considerable cash incentives&#8217; to McLaren, but &#8216;that proved difficult for them to accept, due to competitive forces in some countries, particularly in Germany&#8217;. In return, McLaren would have been able to develop a car as close to the M9 as possible (i.e. only include the optional carbon fibre carbonfibre roof), and have access to BMW&#8217;s research and development centre and design facilities. BMW and McLaren were reportedly unhappy with the deal, although the firm has so far denied making any financial offer.</p>



<p>We&#8217;ll have to wait to see what happens next. BMW&#8217;s M Division is currently producing the M Coupe, the M3, and the M3s GT Coupes.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/this-car-is-alive/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Explain Colours Theory and How They Applied in Real Project.</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/explain-colours-theory-and-how-they-applied-in-real-project/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/explain-colours-theory-and-how-they-applied-in-real-project/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 13:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Good Reads]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Goodreads]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=100</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[I really like purple, but I don&#8217;t do all the design, so I do not really do it because of the amount of work is too hard to do. Also, I used blue, purple, green at some times to help me concentrate on the project. I use brown instead because I am too familiar with [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-drop-cap">I really like purple, but I don&#8217;t do all the design, so I do not really do it because of the amount of work is too hard to do. Also, I used blue, purple, green at some times to help me concentrate on the project. I use brown instead because I am too familiar with it. You have to decide which colours are good choices for the project (and which are not &#8211; you need to think of different scenarios with different applications as this affects how we think about colors and how they are perceived).</p>



<p>Phew! You just said that you didn&#8217;t start making banners until you were 16. What exactly made you think of banners as the way that you would use them?</p>



<p>My mom bought a banner for my birthday. We took a holiday at another house and we spent many hours painting banners (as soon as we finished, I got my new laptop, which I bought with 3,6€).</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>How much time did you spend on creating banners?</p></blockquote>



<p>I started by sketching banner, then working on all the things that I wanted to add. I was really happy with the layout and all that (like the colors).</p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/explain-colours-theory-and-how-they-applied-in-real-project/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
