<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Video Tutorials &#8211; Publisher</title>
	<atom:link href="https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/category/video/video-tutorials/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher</link>
	<description>Publishing platform template for Wordpress</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 15:27:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.4</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Video Tutorials &#8211; Publisher</title>
	<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Walking Illustration Video Self Hosted</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/walking-illustration-video-self-hosted/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/walking-illustration-video-self-hosted/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 09:47:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Video Tutorials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/?p=1780</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The image is from the first game in the series in which the character is an orphan who wanders around town from place to place, carrying a map that shows a winding road, an old abandoned house with a broken front door, and lots of buildings with red roofs and boarded-off windows. Illustrations tutorial&#160;for your [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The image is from the first game in the series in which the character is an orphan who wanders around town from place to place, carrying a map that shows a winding road, an old abandoned house with a broken front door, and lots of buildings with red roofs and boarded-off windows.</p>



<p><strong>Illustrations tutorial</strong>&nbsp;for your next project! Check out our gallery where you can see our portfolio and get an idea of what to get you started.</p>



<p>This is a form of walking where you walk between two places, such as: a supermarket and the beach; or a cafe and a bar.</p>



<p>This is about a mile of walking from point A to point B. This is pretty much the same kind of walking as driving, and in most cases, it is probably the type of walking that gets you the most done. If you&#8217;re used to walking between bus stations for example, this is also the way that you find yourself most often.</p>



<p>We&#8217;ve built an amazing product that was built by people who love the product, have worked with us before to test it, and know us well from their previous work. We&#8217;re working to keep costs low while adding functionality and features that will please our customers. Your support will help us bring this product to life and make it better over time.</p>



<p>Our Kickstarter campaign is a one-time investment, but once funded you&#8217;ll be helping us build a team and a great product that you can&#8217;t afford not to have for yourself.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/walking-illustration-video-self-hosted/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Running on The Road &#8211; A Self Hosted Video</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/running-on-the-road/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/running-on-the-road/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 14:48:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Video Tutorials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Goodreads]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/?p=441</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[My One-Night Stand with a Butterfly&#8216; is probably my favorite album of 2014. A song that&#8217;s only accessible to people who know one of its lyrics. I&#8217;m sure that&#8217;s all true… but it&#8217;s also an example of how things change. The music and the lyrics will always change. We have to move, and we have [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>My One-Night Stand with a Butterfly</strong>&#8216; is probably my favorite album of 2014. A song that&#8217;s only accessible to people who know one of its lyrics.</p>



<p>I&#8217;m sure that&#8217;s all true… but it&#8217;s also an example of how things change. The music and the lyrics will always change.</p>



<p>We have to move, and we have to change. So will we have to move away from this country, to something that&#8217;s completely foreign, not even from our own family, but from the one I was raised in? That&#8217;s the question we&#8217;re asking now, and I think we&#8217;re probably in a pretty dangerous position to just keep talking about, which doesn&#8217;t make it all okay… to talk about, which doesn&#8217;t make us okay…</p>



<p>I&#8217;ve heard that it is.</p>



<p>Now that we know our country, and the things we feel are here, and this country isn&#8217;t the last to be colonized, I wonder how much of this has happened over the years, what it said about us, where our values, our values are relative to these other countries. I wonder how that makes it seem.</p>



<p>It&#8217;s not about sex, drugs or rock &#8216;n&#8217; roll; it&#8217;s about art, love, family, friendship, art and a simple concept: the beauty inside of a human. I&#8217;ve gotten lots of email from artists wanting to collaborate or just collaborate with me, but there is a reason that this particular one has got so many more readers. The reason is because of my &#8220;Betta Fish.&#8221;</p>



<p>The concept is simple. It&#8217;s about how our relationships affect our health. To me, that doesn&#8217;t even have to be art. I love how everyone around me talks about their love of art, but nothing has a chance to work without having an impact if it is simply an individual interaction – that is just a one-night stand. My song &#8216;Moms at Work&#8217; is about one such encounter. &#8220;I met my best friend (on my Betta Fish&#8221;). He&#8217;s my best friend, but he&#8217;ll never tell me the difference because he always thought of me as my &#8216;boyfriend&#8217;.&#8221;</p>



<p>That&#8217;s the essence of &#8216;Betta Fish.&#8217; He knew a lot more than he thought he did, and he loved me for being me and not trying to be more, without feeling like he was controlling the person he was with.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/running-on-the-road/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Grain and noise texture</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/grain-and-noise-texture/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/grain-and-noise-texture/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mangusta Rust]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 09:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Video Tutorials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/?p=1777</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Adding noise to an image is easy and you really can enhance the image. But, to make noise-inducing images that look like nature, sometimes you&#8217;ll want to add some grain. Here are a few ways to add grain to an image that have no effect on your image. If shadows are just not to your [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-drop-cap">Adding noise to an image is easy and you really can enhance the image. But, to make noise-inducing images that look like nature, sometimes you&#8217;ll want to add some grain. Here are a few ways to add grain to an image that have no effect on your image.</p>



<p>If shadows are just not to your taste, or you just want to make a black and white image, then you can add some shadows to your image. You can add a shadow to the left side of the image, by clicking on it, then choose &#8220;Add Shadows&#8221;. You can add a shadow to the top and bottom of the image, or the right and left sides. After adding the shadow, you will see a black circle appear in the image you are working on.</p>



<p>After adding the top and bottom shadow, you will see a black circle appear in the image you are working on.</p>



<p>This technique is also very effective for adding a bit of movement to an image. It&#8217;s best to choose a noise texture and apply it to areas of the image that have a lot of texture, like the leaves of a tree or trees on a mountain.</p>



<p>The technique I&#8217;m going to show here is the first in a series of steps that will eventually show the method behind this tutorial, using a variety of different color palettes to create the various layers of effects.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/grain-and-noise-texture/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Animations and Illustrations are Created</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/how-animations-and-illustrations-are-created/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/how-animations-and-illustrations-are-created/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Demo Account]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 09:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Video Tutorials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/?p=1771</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[For an animation to be able to fit into an app, it has to be able to stand on its own. One way would be if the game engine makes use of an animation on a certain part of the screen and makes use of this in an animation-overlay, but this is unlikely to happen [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>For an animation to be able to fit into an app, it has to be able to stand on its own. One way would be if the game engine makes use of an animation on a certain part of the screen and makes use of this in an animation-overlay, but this is unlikely to happen and requires a game which will not have any visual updates on screen in between the playing sequence itself.</p>



<p>In other words, an animation is not a true independent character which has a name and it&#8217;s animation. An animation is a string of bytes which the animator sets before recording it. The engine (or the application) will then copy the entire animation sequence into the graphics memory of the game, which looks completely different from the final sprite when that happens.</p>



<hr class="wp-block-separator is-style-dots"/>



<p>What is animation and how is it used on a daily basis? Is there a universal answer? What makes an animated story, or scene? To answer these questions and many others, it will help to understand the basic principles and rules of animation. For this course I hope to provide a strong foundation for our future animators as we develop this process.</p>



<hr class="wp-block-separator is-style-dots"/>



<p>In this course, you will learn the general principles of animation in 2 main areas: the process of drawing and composition. In this course you will practice drawing a variety of animated images and learn how to understand the process for constructing and editing them.</p>



<p>Along the way, you&#8217;ll learn fundamental drawing techniques like outline and perspective, how to create and edit animated effects, and how to work with audio, which is one of the important skills you&#8217;ll need in order to produce a great, visually stunning experience. All of us at The Animation Store are artists.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/how-animations-and-illustrations-are-created/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>World Chocolate Day &#8211; Vimeo Video</title>
		<link>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/world-chocolate-day/</link>
					<comments>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/world-chocolate-day/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mangusta Rust]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 05:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Video Tutorials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/?p=1752</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Animate character&#160;or objects to a certain level on the fly. For example: a robot can be put into stasis at a preset level, while a statue can be moved over to another space while an enemy can be put back into stasis. Once the robot or statue goes into stasis, the other robot or statue [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-drop-cap"><strong>Animate character</strong>&nbsp;or objects to a certain level on the fly. For example: a robot can be put into stasis at a preset level, while a statue can be moved over to another space while an enemy can be put back into stasis. Once the robot or statue goes into stasis, the other robot or statue can move over to replace it.</p>



<p><strong>Animating an illustration character</strong>&nbsp;or a simple painting can be as simple as holding your finger over the screen and the screen will animate. This also applies to the ability to add additional text that does not require a separate drawing.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://typer.seventhqueen.com/publisher/world-chocolate-day/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
